[
    {
        "question": "Frage 1?",
        "answer": "Antwort 1."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 2?",
        "answer": "Antwort 2."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 3?",
        "answer": "Antwort 3."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 4?",
        "answer": "Antwort 4."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 5?",
        "answer": "Antwort 5."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 6?",
        "answer": "Antwort 6."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 7?",
        "answer": "Antwort 7."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 8?",
        "answer": "Antwort 8."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 9?",
        "answer": "Antwort 9."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 10?",
        "answer": "Antwort 10."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 11?",
        "answer": "Antwort 11."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 12?",
        "answer": "Antwort 12."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 13?",
        "answer": "Antwort 13."
    },
    {
        "question": "Frage 14?",
        "answer": "Antwort 14."
    }
]